Srinivasan Chakkarapani

Digital Product Designer (UI-UX)

www.srinivasan.design +91 9442941315 tcsreeni93@gmail.com

Summary

I am product designer who loves creating digital products with delightful experiences. Solving problems via digital products has been my passion over the years with a penchant designing interfaces for new age devices like smartphones and wearables. I have a strong belief that a good product is a concoction of design, experience and technology and also making sure it has an impact on people.

Education

M.S - Human Computer Interaction DePaul University, 2020 (Expected)

Bachelors in Computer Science & Engineering SASTRA University, 2015

Professional Experience

Zeta — Interaction Designer - Bangalore, India

February 2018 - August 2018

Worked as as an interaction designer for various products bundled inside the Zeta Optima product which focuses on digitising the employee tax benefits.

Zoho Corporation — Product Designer - Chennai, India

December 2015 - January 2018

Designed and Shipped the Zoho Sheet product as the primary designer. As a key designed I worked on its mobile platforms (i.e.) iOS, Android from ideating features, wireframing to setting visual standards. Worked Closely with the developers, Product managers to effectively ship the product to the respective stores.

Holachef — Product Designer - Mumbai, India

June 2015 - December 2015

Designed the iOS and Android Application for the food tech company. Also wore the hat of web designer in designing the main website of the company. Helped in designing various back end applications that helped the business.

Skillset

User Interface Design

User Experience Design

Interaction Design

User Research

Visual Design

Information Architecture

Tools

Sketch App

Principle

Adobe Creative Suite

Invision Studio

Framer App

Platform experience

iOS

Android

Web Apps

Languages

HTML

CSS

JavaScript